harrietandfriends.com 2016-10-27

# Privacy Policy/ FTC Disclosure

### Your privacy  

Poshonabudget.com/myposhmedia uses Google Analytics and Advertising to collect visitor data and analyze traffic on this site. This information helps us understand visitor interests and helps us improve our website. 

When you visit our site, the pages that you look at, and a short text file called a cookie, are downloaded to your computer. A cookie is used to store small amounts of information. This information is collected for traffic analysis only. The cookie does not contain personal details. The cookies used on this site are for Clickstream/ navigation information only.The information being collected does not contain personally identifiable information and are used to identify patterns. 

Depending on the browser that you use, you can set your preferences to block/ refuse cookies, and/ or notify you before they are placed. This site does not sell, give, or trade the statistics to any 3rd parties for data-mining or marketing purposes. Please visit http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/ for their privacy policy.

Tracking cookies are good as they let us know where you came from, what pages you visited, and how long you stayed. Your name and personal information is never part of this information. This information is beneficial, as it is used to improve this site and it’s content. For example, if enough people seem to be interested in recipes or fashion, more posts will be made to help you enjoy these topics even more. 

Cookies collect information about your surfing habits only on the site of the provider of the cookie. Please visit your browser’s policy on how to block cookies if you would like to not take part in the tracking on this site. Experts say that these cookies are not harmful and cannot introduce viruses or extract personal contact information.

Advertisers on this site may also be using cookies.  
This site has no access to these cookies and no information on the specifics. Please consult the advertiser for more information on this. 

This site sells nothing from this site specifically. No personal information related to sales is needed or used. If you have subscribed to the newsletter or social media of this site, the information that you have provided is never shared for monetary purposes. We value our readers privacy.

### Disclosure Policy

This policy is valid from 23 February 2013

**As per the FTC guidelines for blogs,  
**  
This blog accepts forms of cash advertising, sponsorship, paid insertions or other forms of compensation.

This blog abides by word of mouth marketing standards. We believe in honesty of relationship, opinion and identity. The compensation received may influence the advertising content, topics or posts made in this blog. That content, advertising space or post will be clearly identified as paid or sponsored content.

The owner(s) of this blog is compensated to provide opinion on products, services, websites and various other topics. Even though the owner(s) of this blog receives compensation for our posts or advertisements, we always give our honest opinions, findings, beliefs, or experiences on those topics or products. The views and opinions expressed on this blog are purely the bloggers’ own. Any product claim, statistic, quote or other representation about a product or service should be verified with the manufacturer, provider or party in question.

This blog does not contain any content which might present a conflict of interest.

r
